[{"id": 1250, "question": "A woman wears a face mask to protect her from polluted air in prefix = st1 /Lanzhou,China, in December. A new study showed air pollution might put people more at risk for heart disease than scientists had thought. Kristin Miller, a doctoral student at the UniversityofWashington, said chances of getting the disease were related to not only which city a woman lived in, but also where in the city. The study found that the effects of air pollution were often larger within cities than between cities. The new findings make experts suspect that current pollution limits may be inadequate. Scientists examined rates of heart attack, stroke and other cardiovascular events in women with long-term exposure to air pollution. The study involved women over the age of fifty who had no sign of cardiovascula...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["air pollution is more serious than scientists thought", "the control of air pollution is effective in some cities", "people throughout a city have the same risk of getting heart diseases", "air pollution affects women more than men"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1746, "question": "\"Colour\" and \"color1\" , \"favourite\" and \"favorite\"\"- Have you ever wondered why Americans spell those words without a \"u\"? Is it because they are lazy? Of course not.In fact, the difference in spelling was created by Noah Webster(1758--1843) .He is a teacher who reformed English to make American identity stronger.Linguists celebrated his 250th birthday on October 16,2008.After the Revolutionary War(1775--1783) , Webster believed that Americans should have their own dictionary, rather than rely on British versions.He dropped the British \"u\" in some words.And he changed \"centre\" into \"center\" for children to learn English by spelling words more like they sounded. Webster wasn't shy about expressing his opinions.In defining preposterous (unreasonable) , he wrote: \"A Republican government in t...\n\nQ: Which of the following would probably be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Webster's dictionary", "American identity", "The shaper of American English", "Spelling differences between American and British English"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1491, "question": "It is the goal of politicians everywhere-----how to win and keep the trust of voters. Now researchers at the University of St Anurew's in Scotland say they may have the answer. They believe politicians could learn a lot from recent advances in science. A growing number of studies have shown that people do judge a book by its cover. Researchers say most of us make quick judgments about a person on the basis of how they look. Studies suggest that people are less likely to trust those with particularly masculine features, such as a square jaw, small eyes or a big nose. \" They are considered dominant and less trustworthy,\" says Ms Cornwell. \"It doesn't mean that men who look more masculine are less trustworthy-----it's just our first impression.\" Those with less masculine features-----larger e...\n\nQ: What's the best title for the passage?", "options": ["How Science could Help Politicians", "How to Win the Trust of Voters", "The Other Sides of Politicians", "An Important Discovery for Politicians"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 276, "question": "This year, some twenty-three hundred teenagers from all over the world will spend about ten months in their US homes. They will attend US schools, meet US teenagers, and form impressions of the real America. At the same time, about thirteen hundred American teenagers will go to other countries to learn new languages and gain a new understanding of the rest of the world. Here is a two-way students exchange in action. Fred, nineteen, spent last year in Germany with George's family. In turn, George's son Mike spent a year in Fred's home in America. Fred knew little German when he arrived, but after two months' study, the language began to come to him. School was completely different from what he had expected --- much harder. Students rose respectfully when a teacher entered the room. They too...\n\nQ: After experiencing the American school life, Mike thought   _  .", "options": ["better education should include something good from both American and German schools", "German schools trained students to be better citizens", "American schools were not as good as German ones", "the easy life in American schools was more helpful to students"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2618, "question": "In the dark and damp market,Chen ShuChu,near her sixties,owns a stall that her father left her.The stall,called YuanJin Vegetables,is her everything.Chen earns only a little money by selling vegetables,but she has donated about $321,550 to help poor children. In March,Forbes magazine named her one of the 48 great philanthropists from the AsiaPacific region.A month later,TIME magazine selected the year's top 100 influential people and Chen was one of them.Although she has received many honours and rewards,Chen only cares about her vegetable stall and whether her regular customers buy her vegetables or not.\"I do not place great importance on money.When I donate to help others,I feel happy and I can sleep well at night.\" Chen said. Chen's ability to donate such a great deal of money has led m...\n\nQ: In Chen's eyes,a luxury is about  _  .", "options": ["any form of enjoyment", "doing what she wants", "gaining material benefits", "everything except food and a bed"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 813, "question": "Have you heard of the scandal that happened in one of Great Britain's biggest supermarket chains called Tesco? The British love Tesco as it sells very cheap products and it can be found on almost every corner of a British city or town. On January 15th 2013 food inspectors discovered 30 % horsemeat in a certain brand of frozen beefburgers that were mostly sold by Tesco in the UK and Ireland. In times of social media like Facebook and Twitter the news has spread fast and customers have been very concerned about what the food they buy actually contains. Tesco said it had taken away the burgers from the shop shelves immediately, and apologized to their customers. They also promised that they would find out what exactly happened and that they would work harder than ever so this would never happ...\n\nQ: What didn't Tesco do in response to the scandal?", "options": ["It withdrew the beefburgers.", "It made an apology to the public.", "It investigated and found out the cause and effect of the scandal.", "It returned money to customers who bought the beefburgers."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1297, "question": "Nervous suspects locked up in Britain's newest police station may feel relieved by a pleasant yellow color on the door . If they are close to confessing a crime , the blue on the wall might _ . Gwent Police have abandoned colors such as greys and browns of the 20th-century police cell and have used color psychology to decorate them . Ystrad Mynach station , which recently opened at a cost of PS5 million has four cells with glass doors for prisoners who suffer from claustrophobia . Designers have painted the frames yellow , which researchers say is a calming color . Other cells contain a royal blue line because psychologists believe that the color is likely to encourage truthfulness . The station has 31 cells , including 12 with a \"live scan\" system for drunken or disturbed prisoners , whic...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly concerned with   _   .", "options": ["the relationship between colors and psychology", "a comparison of different functions of colors", "the use of colors in cells to affect criminals' psychology", "scientific ways to help criminals reform themselves in prison"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 287, "question": "Born in America in 1898, William was an extraordinary boy, gifted with an amazing IQ between 250 and 300. The genius went to a grammar school when he was only 6 years old and graduated just within 7 months. At the age of 11, he became the youngest student of the Harvard University. He graduated with high scores at the age of 16 and entered Harvard Law School at 18. Gifted with an amazing IQ between 220 and 230, Terence Tao makes it to this list of the people with the highest IQ in the world. Born in Adelaide, Australia in 1975, this genius first displayed his incredible intelligence at a mere age of 2, when he managed to solve basic arithmetic questions on his own. At the age of 16, he graduated with both Master's and Bachelor's degrees at the Flinders University. He has been considered as...\n\nQ: From the passage we can know that  _  .", "options": [".when William graduated from the Harvard University, he got the highest scores", "at the age of 2, Terence solved basic arithmetic questions on his own", "Christopher Hirata is a Japanese", "researchers have found out why Albert Einstein was so brilliant"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3066, "question": "A single letter written by Albert Einstein was sold for more than $400, 000. But could an e-mail printout or an electronic file reach similar heights? That's the question facing those who deal in the literary artifacts of public figures, as they struggle to work out how to do business in the electronic world where information can be copied and spread out more easily than ever before. \"Booksellers, collectors and libraries are already trading in digital objects,\" Joan Winterkorn, a researcher told people. When Emory University Library bought author Slaman Rushdie's archives in 2006, it received a desktop computer, three laptops, a hard drive and a smart phone along with his paper flies. And the writer John Updike, who died last month, started using computers in the 1980s, Winterkorn pointed...\n\nQ: What is the author's attitude towards the trade in electronic documents?", "options": ["Negative.", "Positive.", "Neutral.", "Hopeful."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 91, "question": "If there is a building which symbolizes a country--such as the Eiffel Tower for France and Sydney Opera House for Australia--then it has to be the Taj Mahal for India. It was set up by Emperor Shah Jahan in 1653 in memory of his wife, Mumtaz Mahal. From the time they got married, they wouldn't be separated. She followed him to wars, advised him on affairs of state, and was loved by his people for her good work. But she died in 1631 during childbirth. The emperor was heart-broken and had the Taj Mahal built as a sign of his love. It took more than 20 years for the Taj Mahal to be built. Workers were brought in, not only from all over India, but from Central Asia too. A total of 20,000 people worked on the building. In 1657, Shah Jahan fell ill, and in 1658 his son Aurangzeb, imprisoned his ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, we know that Shah Jahan   _  .", "options": ["lived a hard life in his last few years", "lost his life just because of his old age", "was not popular with his people at that time", "treated his son badly when he was young"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 984, "question": "People can be addicted to different things -- e.g. alcohol, drug, certain foods, or even television. People who have such an addiction are compulsive :They have a very powerful psychological need that they feel they must satisfy. According to psychologists, many people are compulsive spenders. They feel that they must spend money. This compulsion, like most others, is impossible to explain reasonably. For compulsive spenders who buy on credit , charge accounts are even more exciting than money. In other words, compulsive spenders feel that with credit, they can do anything. Their pleasure in spending large amounts is actually greater than the pleasure that they get from the things they buy. There is even a special psychology of bargain hunting. To save money, of course, most people look fo...\n\nQ: According to the psychologists, a compulsive spender is one who spends large amounts of money  _  .", "options": ["and takes great pleasure from what he or she buys", "in order to satisfy his or her basic needs in life", "just to meet his or her strong psychological need", "and feels he or she is cheated"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3282, "question": "Boxing was long viewed sickly. Generally forbidden by law in earlier days, the fighting was usually done with bare fists, and matches often lasted forty or fifty rounds. In 1882 John L. Sullivan, a fighter of great power, won the world heavyweight championship from Paddy Ryan in a bare fisted battle marked by hitting, scratching, and biting without any rule. Five years later, while fighting Patsy Cardiff at Minneapolis, Sullivan broke his right arm in the third round, but he continued fighting to the sixth round and won. In 1889, Sullivan defeated Jade Kilrain with his bare fists in another championship fight, winning twenty thousand dollars and a diamond prize medal. His admirers talked then of running him for the next governor, but he traveled to Australia for a boxing tour instead, comi...\n\nQ: Sullivan was so popular that his admirers   _  .", "options": ["encouraged him to be a governor", "raised twenty thousand dollars for him", "advised him to take boxing tour of Australia", "refused to believe he could be defeated"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2728, "question": "Manchester is the \"capital\" of the northwest of England. Situated on the east bank of the River Irwell, it is a lively busy city with a large student population. Although it was once seen as only a dull industrial place, in recent years Manchester has become the \"in\" place. It is well-known for its clubs, its fashion and its music, not to mention its world -famous football team, Manchester United. There is plenty to see in Manchester and something to suit all taste. For example, you have a taste of the Orient in Chinatown, home to Manchester's large Chinese population. Another place to visit is the historical Eastlefield area, which contains the first urban heritage park in Britain. Here you can walk around the museums and experience the atmosphere of the 19thcentury Manchester. Football f...\n\nQ: According to the passage, Manchester is   _  .", "options": ["a big city in the southwest of England", "only known for its heavy industry", "interesting only if you like football", "a very popular place now"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2859, "question": "Homeschooling is the education of children at home, typically by parents but sometimes by tutors, rather than in public or private school. As a matter of fact, most childhood education occurred within the family or community. Homeschooling is a legal choice for parents in developed countries to provide their children with a learning environment at home. Parents see many reasons for homeschool, including better test results, improved instruction, to help the public system with fewer kids, poor public school environment, religious reasons, improved character development, the expense of private education, and objection to what is taught locally in public school. Homeschooling can also be a choice for families living in remote locations, living abroad, and to allow for more traveling. Also man...\n\nQ: According to the text, some parents choose to homeschool their children because   _  .", "options": ["they are tired of taking their children to and from school", "their children are too naughty to go to a regular school", "they are not satisfied with what is taught at local public schools", "they have too many children to feed and educate"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 484, "question": "I recently turned fifty, which is young for a tree, midlife for an elephant, and ancient for a sportsman. Fifty is a nice number for the states in the US or for a national speed limit but it is not a number that I was prepared to have hung on me. Fifty is supposed to be my father's age, but now I am stuck with this number and everything it means. A few days ago, a friend tried to cheer me up by saying, \" Fifty is what forty used to be.\" He had made an inspirational point, Am I over the hill?People keep telling me that the hill has been moved, and I keep telling them that he high-jump bar has dropped from the six feet I once easily cleared to the four feet that is impossible for me now. \" Your are not getting older, you are getting better.\" says Dr. Joyce Brothers. This, however, is the kin...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that", "options": ["the old should led a simple life", "the old should face the fact of aging", "the old should take more exercise", "the old should fill themselves with curiosity"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3297, "question": "Do you feel embarrassed when your mum tries to use slang or when she calls you by your childhood nickname in front of your friends? And how about searching for the nearest exit when your father dances with joy when he finds his favorite CD in the shop? Loving them dearly doesn't prevent you from feeling uncomfortable around them. And parents have to accept that Adam Gopnick, a writer for the New Yorker magazine, said in an article published by the BBC: ''The one thing that is written into the human genome is that exactly at the age of 13, your child... will discover that you are now the most embarrassing, ridiculous and annoying person on the planet.'' A survey by the site YoungPoll.com in 2010 suggested that one in three youngsters is so _ by their parents that they refuse to be seen with...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following deeds will make a teenager feel bad?", "options": ["His parents ask him to do housework.", "His parents show up in the public.", "His parents hold his hands before his friends.", "A child reaches the age of 13."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2257, "question": "To me, the ocean is our greatest wilderness. I love swimming in it , surfing its waves, watching it from shore and thinking about all the life living unseen under the surface. When I take my little kids to check out tide pools, we're overjoyed when we find a sea star or some shellfish. Lately, though, I've noticed a change in my favorite pools: there are more sea grasses and fewer animals with shells. I can't help feeling these small changes _ something more troubling about our oceans. It matches what scientists are telling us: our oceans are being troubled by carbon dioxide that threatens corals, colorful fish, salmon, sea otters, even whales. Our oceans are facing a major change. Every hour, a million tons of carbon dioxide from cars, factories and power plants rain down on the world's o...\n\nQ: What the author worries about most is   _   .", "options": ["the harm of sea grasses", "carbon pollution in the sea", "that the petition may be turned down", "how fishermen can make a living in the future"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1313, "question": "Mountaineers have noted that as they climb, for example, up to the 12,633foot Humphreys Peak in Arizona, plant life changes greatly. In the Sonoran Desert, one climbs into a pine forest at 7,000 feet and a treeless tundra on the top of the mountain. It may seem that plants at a given altitude are associated in what can be called \"communities\" -groupings of species. The idea is that over time, plants that require particular climate and soil conditions come to live in the same places, and are frequently to be found together. Scientists study the history of plant life and build up a picture of how groups of plants have responded to climate changes and how ecosystems develop. But are these associations, _ are real in the present, permanent? A great natural experiment took place on this planet ...\n\nQ: All of the following are true EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["The ice age occurred when there were small changes in the orbit of the earth", "fossil records seem to indicate that plants will be preserved if they have enough room to move", "fossil records clearly show that entire groups of plants are unlikely to have moved together", "in the ice age glaciers covered the world to depths of up to two miles"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1496, "question": "Love Is Just a Thread Sometimes I really doubt whether there is love between my parents.Every day they are very busy trying to earn money to pay the high tuition for us.They don't act in the romantic ways that I read in books or I see on TV.\" I love you\" is too luxurious for them to say .Sending flowers to each other on Valentine's Day is even more _ .My father is easy to lose his temper, especially when he's very tired from the hard work. One day, my mother was sewing a quilt.I silently sat beside her and asked her if there was love between them.\" What?\" she replied, still doing her work.My mother stopped her work and raised her head with surprise.She didn't answer immediately.Then she bowed her head and continued sewing the quilt.I was in a great embarrassment and I didn't know what to d...\n\nQ: What can we learn from her mother's answer about love?", "options": ["Love should be seen anywhere.", "Love should be seen anytime.", "Love should be a thread.", "Love is really existing everywhere and anytime even though we can't feel it."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3217, "question": "Researchers in the psychology department at the University of California at Los Angeles (UCLA) have discovered a major difference in the way men and women respond to stress. This difference may explain why men are more likely to suffer from stress-related disorders. Until now, psychological research has maintained that both men and women have the same \"fight-or-flight\" reaction to stress. In other words, individuals either react with aggressive behavior, such as verbal or physical conflict (\"fight\"), or they react by withdrawing from the stressful situation (\"flight\"). However, the UCLA research team found that men and women have quite different biological and behavioral responses to stress. While men often react to stress in the fight-or-flight response, women often have another kind of r...\n\nQ: Which of the following might be the best title of the passage?", "options": ["How men and women get over stress", "How men and women suffer from stress", "How researchers overcome stress problems", "How researchers handle stress-related disorders"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1420, "question": "Farmer Joe was in his cart when he was hit by a truck. He decided his injuries from the accident were serious enough to take the trucking company to court. In court the trucking company's lawyer was questioning farmer Joe. \"Didn't you say, at the scene of the accident, 'I'm fine'?\" said the lawyer. Farmer Joe responded, \"Well, I'll tell you what happened. I had just loaded my favorite donkey Bessie into the....\" \"I didn't ask for any details,\" the lawyer interrupted, \"just answer the question. Didn't you say, at the scene of the accident, 'I'm fine'?\" Farmer Joe said, \"Well I had just got Bessie into the cart and I was driving down the road....\" The lawyer interrupted again and said, \"Judge, I am trying to establish the fact that, at the scene of the accident, this man told the highway pol...\n\nQ: According to the passage, why did the policeman shot the donkey?", "options": ["Because he wanted Farmer Joe to keep silent about the accident.", "Because he thought it was the best way to stop the donkey from suffering.", "Because the donkey's groaning was too loud.", "Because he wanted to make Farmer Joe feel better."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 177, "question": "A gentleman put an advertisement in a newspaper for a boy to work in his office. Out of the nearly fifty men who come to apply, the man selected one and dismissed the others. \"I should like to know,\" said a friend, \"the reason you preferred that boy, who brought not a single letter--not a recommendation ,\" \"You are wrong\" said the gentleman. He had a great man. He wiped his feet at the door and closed the door after him, indicating that he was careful. He gave his seat immediately to that old man, showing that he was kind and thoughtful. He took off his cap when he came in and answered my questions, showing that he was polite and gentlemanly. \" All the rest stepped over the book which I had purposely put on the floor.\" He picked it up and placed it on the table; and he waited quietly for h...\n\nQ: According to the passage, we know that the gentleman hired the boy  _  .", "options": ["not by his letters but by his good manners", "by the relationship between them", "by the feelings", "by his letters"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2660, "question": "Along a long path we came to a deep valley, on the far side of which the path led into some very thick bushes. Rather than push through up again and rejoin the path on the far side of the bushes As I climbed down into the valley a bird flew off h rock on which I had put my hand. On looking at the spot from which the bird had risen, I saw two eggs. They were the kind that I did not have in my collection, so I placed them carefully in my bag, wrapped in a little dry grass. As we went further down the valley the sides became steeper and not far from where I had entered. It came to drop of about twelve to fourteen feet. The water that rushed down all these small valleys in the rainy season had worn the rock as glass. As it was too deep to climb down, I handed my gun to one of the men and slid ...\n\nQ: At the end of the story, the writer knew that   _  .", "options": ["a tiger had run away", "a tiger was close to them", "the men had seen a tiger", "a tiger had seen them"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3222, "question": "Thomas Brodie-Sangster's cars and action figures weren't just toys. \"They would always be characters, and I would always put on stupid voices,\" says Thomas (Born on 16 May 1990). For him, acting was just a matter of moving childhood games to a set. Maturity and independence came to Thomas early as he started work at ten. After his first audition , he learned about _ . Though hurt and disappointed, he took a part in a tiny, unknown TV film in 2001. No one noticed his performance - no one except screenwriter Richard Curtis. Two years later, he played Sam, a twelve-year-old in love in Curtis's Love Actually. After that hit film, he played actor Colin Firth's son in Nanny McPhee. Firth then joined a film called The Last Legion and supported Thomas for its lead role. As a result, the boy played...\n\nQ: Thomas played the lead role in   _  .", "options": ["Love Actually", "Games of Thrones", "The Last Region", "Nanny McPhee"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 839, "question": "Individuality is the particular character, or aggregate (total) of qualities that distinguishes one person or thing from others. Many artists late in the last century were in search of a means to express their individuality. Modern dance was one of the ways some of these people sought to free their creative spirit. At the beginning there was no exacting technique, no foundation from which to build. In later years, trial, error and genius founded the techniques and the principles of the movement. Eventually, innovators even drew from what they considered the dread ballet, but first they had to get rid of all that was academic so that the new could be discovered. The beginnings of modern dance were happening before Isadora Duncan, but she was the first person to bring the new dance to genera...\n\nQ: According to the passage, what did nature represent to Isadora Duncan?", "options": ["Something to conquer.", "A model for movement.", "A place to find peace.", "A symbol of disorder."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 904, "question": "When Charles Strattion was five, he stopped growing. His mother took him to see the famous showman, P. T. Barnum, and thought a small person would be the perfect addition to his show. He hired Charles' parents along with him, and they traveled around the world together. He gave the two-foot-tall Charles a new name, general Tom Thumb. He taught Tom how to sing, dance, act, and tell jokes. When he felt Tom was ready to perform on stage, he made up ads. To stir up great interest, he said that Tom was eleven years old and had come from England. Tom's act was very popular and brought in a lot of money. By the time Tom was an adult, he had grown very rich. He had become a billionaire at the age of twenty-five. Fortunately for Tom, Mr. Barnum added more little people to his show, and Tom became l...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the best description of the fact that Tom was smart?", "options": ["He became a billionaire at twenty-five", "He learned how to sing, dance, and act at a very young age.", "He met with President Lincoln during his honeymoon", "He married a school teacher."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 137, "question": "Dear Earthmen , I have enjoyed my stay on your interesting unusual planet. I think I understand the life on earth now and I would like to give you my impressions. First of all you live in boxes. Every morning you leave your big boxes and get into smaller boxes on wheels. All these small boxes race around and around, and finally stop to rest. You then leave these boxes on wheels and go to very large tall boxes. After testing all days you get back in your little boxes and return to your big boxes. There you sit and stare at tiny glowing boxes with moving pictures on the front. Only one thing puzzles me. One day I went to a football game. A bunch of angry boys fought over a little round ball. Everyone yelled for them to stop but they kept on fighting. They were angry, I suppose, about being c...\n\nQ: The tiny glowing boxes with moving pictures on the front are  _  .", "options": ["cameras", "cinema screens", "TV sets", "telescopes"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1493, "question": "The SAT is one of two major tests for the entrance to American colleges and universities. The other test is called the ACT. More than 2 million students take the SAT yearly, including about 100,000 foreign students. The organization of the SAT will change the entrance test in 2016. The College Board announced that the new SAT will no longer test students on rarely used words. But it will include passages from American historical documents or from writings on freedom and human rights. The College Board says words on the new test will be related to usage. Students will be asked to tell the meaning of words according to the context of the reading passages. Nigerian student Peace Umoru is in her first year at Howard University. She says the rarely used words are the hardest part for internatio...\n\nQ: The new SAT could be more difficult for international students because  _  .", "options": ["they are short of skills and abilities", "they often perform badly in college", "they know nothing about American history", "they have different cultural backgrounds"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3382, "question": "Tayka Hotel De Sal Where: Tahua, Bolivia How much: About $95 a night Why it's cool: You've stayed at hotels made of brick or wood, but salt? That's something few can claim. Tayka Hotel de Sal is made totally of salt -- including the beds (though you'll sleep on regular mattresses and blankets). The hotel sits on the Salar de Uyuni, a prehistoric dried-up lake that's the world's biggest salt flat. Builders use the salt from the 4,633-square-mile flat to make the bricks, and glue them together with a paste of wet salt that hardens when it dries. When rain starts to dissolve the hotel, the owners just mix up more salt paste to strengthen the bricks. Green Magic Nature Resort Where: Vythiri, India How much: About $240 a night Why it's cool: Riding a pulley -operated lift 86 feet to your treeto...\n\nQ: Which of the hotel makes you have a feeling of living in the far past?", "options": ["Tayka Hotel De Sal", "Green Magic Nature Resort", "Dog Bark Park Inn B&B", "Gamirasu Cave Hotel"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 309, "question": "When we say older people shrink, we don't mean they become tiny enough to fit in your pocket! We just mean that it's common for older people to become a little shorter over time. This kind of shrinking can't be reversed, although people can slow or stop this process. But why does shrinking happen at all? Because of gravity (the force that keeps your feet on the ground) , cushions between the bones in the spine , get compressed , which makes a person lose a little height and become shorter. Another reason why some older people shrink is because of osteoporosis . Osteoporosis occurs when bone is broken down and not enough new bone material is made. Over time, bone is said to be lost because it's not being replaced. Bones become smaller and weaker and can easily break if someone with osteopor...\n\nQ: What is the topic of the passage?", "options": ["How can we stop shrinking?", "Why do we shrink?", "Some tips on how to keep tall.", "How to live a healthy life."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3429, "question": "I was at a busy traffic crossing waiting to cross to the other side. There was a family--a man, his wife and an old lady, waiting to cross with me. Then, the light turned green and all of us walked quickly across the road. The light lasted very short, and changed into red in no time. I noticed that both the man and his wife had crossed along with me and the old lady was left behind. I quickly realized what happened. When the light turned dreen again, I ran over to the other side, offered the old lady my right hand and we quickly walked together to the other side of the road. I used my left hand to stop any oncoming traffic so that even if the crossing signal turned red, we cuold make it to the other side safely. In the meantime, both the man and his wife realized that they had left the old...\n\nQ: What does the auther cherish to this day ?", "options": ["The opportunity that he helped the old lady.", "The words the old lady said to him.", "The big smile the old lady gave him.", "The warm handshake the old lady gave him."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1779, "question": "Shoplifting is happening in stores or supermarkets throughout the world. However, shoplifting happens more in British stores, according to a recent research, by the UK-based Center for Retail Research. Napoleon once considered prefix = st1 /Britainas \"a nation of shopkeepers\", to which so many people dreamed of traveling. Now it seems it is a nation of shoplifters. According to the research,Britainis the most light-fingered country in Europe, with nearly one in every two cases of shoplifting across the continent taking place in British stores. The report said there were nearly 566,000 reported cases of shoplifting inBritainout of a Europe-wide total of 1.27 million. The next worst countries in Europe,FranceandGermany, came well belowBritainwith only 188,000 and 167,000 cases, respectively....\n\nQ: According to the passage, in which country are we likely to feel safer when shopping?", "options": ["Britain", "Germany", "France", "Switzerland"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2400, "question": "European Work Experience Program(E.W.E.P.)is an independent British organization which began in 1991 in the city of London.E.W.E.P.provides the opportunity for students from the 25 countries of the European Union and nationals from Norway,Iceland,Switzerland and Liechtenstein to live in England,to gain work experience,to practice their English and to get a better insight into the British social and eulturallife. To apply you must meet the following requirements: *Preferred age: 18 to 28 years old *Be able to work in the UK for a period of at least two months. *Must have a good knowledge of English. *Due to work permit restrictions,European Work Experience Program Ltd will only select you if you are a European Union Member or national from Norway,Iceland,Switzerland and Liechtenstein. Europ...\n\nQ: If you apply for the program.you  _  .", "options": ["must be 18 to 26 years old", "must be able to speak at least three languages", "must be nationals from the countries mentioned in the text", "should have some working experience in a foreign country"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1477, "question": "A person named Bernard Jackson today is a free man, but he has many bitter memories. He spent five years in prison after a jury wrongly convicted (...) him of raping two women. At Jackson's trial, although two witnesses testified that Jackson was with them in another location at the time of the crime, he was convicted anyway. Why? The jury believed the testimony of the two victims, who positively identified Jackson as the man who had attacked them. The court eventually freed Jackson after the police found the real criminal. Many factors influence the accuracy of eyewitness testimony. For instance, witnesses sometimes see photographs of several suspects before they try to identify the person they saw in a group of people. They can become confused by seeing many photographs of similar faces....\n\nQ: Bernard Jackson was found guilty and sentenced 5 years' prison because   _   .", "options": ["the victims insisted that he was the attacker", "he admitted the crime of raping two women", "the police discovered evidence leading to his guilt", "the eyewitness proved the victims' testimony"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2686, "question": "Silk production has a long and colourful history unknown to most people. Scientific discoveries have shown that silk production existed in China from around 2500 B.C., although it could be much older. For hundreds of years, China kept the secret of silk to itself as one for the most closely protected secrets in history. Anyone revealing the secret of silkworms or trying to take silkworm eggs out of ancient China was punished by death. At one time silk was reserved only for the Chinese emperor. Gradually, others began wearing silk. In addition to being used for clothing, silk came to have industrial uses in ancient China, something that happened in the West only in modern times. Silk was used to make musical instruments, fishing lines, weapons, ropes and even paper. During the Han Dynasty s...\n\nQ: Which of the following uses of silk is NOT mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["A way of purchasing goods people sold.", "A material used for making different products.", "A method of paying money to the government.", "A valuable gift given to foreigners travelling in China."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 205, "question": "Reading can be a social activity. Think of the people who belong to book groups. They choose books to read and then meet m discuss them. Now, the website BookCrossing.com rums the page on the traditional idea of a book group. Members go on the site and register books they own that they would like.sham. BookCrossing provides an identifying numb\" .stick inside the book. Then the person 'releases' the book by leaving it in a public place. The hope is that the book will have an adventure, traveling far and wide with each new reader who finds it. Bruce Pederson is the chief executive of BookCrossing. He and his wife Hearer started the site with Ron Hombaker in 2001. Mr. Pederson says, \"One of the founding principles was the two things that change your life: tha people you meet and the books you...\n\nQ: People who find a book from BookCrossing are expected to  _  .", "options": ["send entails to the owner of the book", "make some comments on the book", "keep the book for himself after reading", "leave another book where the book was found"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1295, "question": "In many countries today, laws protect wildlife. In India the need for such protection was realized centuries ago. About 300 B.C. an Indian writer described forests that were somewhat like national parks today. The killing of game animals was carefully governed. Some animals were fully protected. Within the forest, nobody was allowed to cut trees, burn wood, or trap animals for their furs. Animals that became dangerous to human visitors were trapped or killed outside the park, so that other animals would not become uneasy. The need for wildlife protection is greater now than ever before. About a thousand sorts of animals are in danger of extinction, and the speed at which they are being destroyed has been putting on. With mammals, for example, the speed of extinction is now about one sort e...\n\nQ: The word\" extinction\"in this report most properly means\"  _  \" .", "options": ["falling down", "dying out", "growing up", "going away"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2718, "question": "Holiday houses in Mallorca sailing and fishing port - quiet even in summer season. Beautifully situated houses with sights of sea and mountains, yet near to shops and restaurants. Cars and bicycles for hire. Sailing and sports clubs nearby. ITALY IN COMFORT Luxury coach( - carriage) trips of Italy, out of normal holiday season. 21days to visit five Italian cities starting from London 1 st May, 1 st September . The trips are guided by profess or Martin Davis. Head of Italian Studies, London University . See the arts and culture of historic Italy. KIBBUTZ HOLIDAYS IN ISRAEL Working holidays on a kibbutz( co -operative farm) in Israel. All nationalities welcome for one to three months, if prepared to work morning with kibbutz members. Accommodation , food and trips to historic sights all prov...\n\nQ: The most suitable place where Peter and Maria can enjoy their holiday would be  _", "options": ["an Italian city", "a kibbutz in Israel", "a Caribbean island", "the port in Mallorca"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1574, "question": "\"Humans have a code of ethics ,\" says Marc Bekoff, an animal behavior expert at the University of Colorado. \" If I don't play in a certain way, you won't play with me. Some animals have the same code.\" Scientists recently discovered that animals that live in groups, such as elephants, foxes, and wolves, are especially likely to follow rules. If they don't, and each does its own thing, the group might break apart. Group members would be forced to live alone. Then they'd have a harder time hunting and raising their young. That's probably why a traveling wolf pack stopped and waited to let its slowly moving leader catch up. Similar social ties may have caused a captive elephant to save her friend from drowning. Selfish reasons certainly motivated the male fox, who wanted to keep playing. Some...\n\nQ: Some animals living in groups are similar to humans in  _  .", "options": ["feeling good about going out of their way", "playing with each other", "raising their young", "following certain rules"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2055, "question": "From the same place that brought you the Robot Suit HAL comes the \"motorized knee\".Designed by researchers at Japan's Tsukuba University, the device supports the flex( ) of the knee, which enables a runner to use 30% less muscle power compared to running unassisted. Coming in a kit , the device consists of a small motor that helps flex the knee, a sensor that detects the knees' degree of flex, and a safety lever --all of which attach to the user's leg.The user is also forced to carry a backpack that holds a control unit and battery to power the motor.All up the device weighs around 5kg,which will probably lessen the performance benefits of wearing the device somewhat.In experiments runners wearing the device could jog at 7.5kmh, which is hardly anything special--but predictably they could ...\n\nQ: In the author's opinion, the device  _  .", "options": ["should specially serve the disabled", "won't be popular with people at all", "does harm to its user's health", "may not sell as well as expected"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3029, "question": "A news release is a tool of communication,through which information is passed to even the farthest end of the world.It keeps us well informed of the happenings of the world which would otherwise remain unknown. When writing a news release,keep in mind that the media receive hundreds of releases every day.Try to follow these guidelines:Keep it short and professional.Come up with a _ headline that will grasp someone's attention.Sometimes the title will take more time to come up with than writing the release.That's okay-the headline could be critical for getting an event covered! Cover the 5 W's in your first paragraph.Those are who you are; what you are doing;where,when you are doing;why you are doing it,which help us understand the details about the event.Besides,any opinions in the news re...\n\nQ: What's the main purpose of the passage?", "options": ["To tell us the importance of the news release.", "To tell us how to avoid mistakes in the news release.", "To make us know how to make the news release.", "To ask us to read news release on the latest events."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3491, "question": "Have you ever suddenly felt that someone you knew was in trouble--and was he? Have you ever dreamed something that came true later? Maybe you have ESP . ESP stands for Extra Sensory Perception. It may be called a sixth sense. It seems to let people know about events before they happen, or events that are happening some distance away. Here's an example. A woman was ironing clothes. Suddenly she screamed, \"My father is dead! I saw him sitting in the chair!\" Just then, a telegram came. The woman's father died of a heart attack. He died sitting in a chair. There are thousands of stories like this one on record. Scientists are studying them to find out what's behind these strange mental messages. Here's another example--one of hundreds of dreams that have come true: A man dreamed he was walking...\n\nQ: By studying ESP, scientists may get to  _  .", "options": ["learn how people tell lies", "know more about human dreams", "know more about human mind", "learn how strange things happen"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3218, "question": "When you were a child you had a pure mind which was free from worries and anxieties. However, as time goes by, you're faced with so many problems in life. Below are five techniques that can help you get relaxed. 1. Mind your own business. Yes, please mind your own business. When you start being concerned about things which are not related to you, you lose your control on your thought process, which often has negative results disturbing the mental peace. Basically, your mind starts wandering here and there. So next time an unnecessary thought comes to your mind, think whether this is really something you should be worrying for? If not, keep it away and focus on something positive, practical and fruitful. 2. Surround yourself with positive people. _ negative comments and stay away from negat...\n\nQ: This passage is written for those who want to   _  .", "options": ["seek learning skills", "find positive people as friends", "make their mind pure", "get mentally peaceful and relaxed"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1087, "question": "Coaches and parents always tell us to keep our goals in mind when we go for a competition. Carrying your goals and expectations into a competition is one of the biggest mistakes any athlete can make. This is a big game and you want to win. You want to score a hundred, defeat your competitors, or score a hat-trick of goals. When you carry your goals into the competitive ground with you, chances are great that you will leave that performance with disappointment and heartache, and nothing more! Expectations will _ Expectations will distract you from the performance and make your muscles tighten up. Want to perform to your potential when it counts the most? Then write your goals on a piece of paper before you leave for the game, match or race, and then leave that paper at home! Make a deal wit...\n\nQ: According to the passage, for an athlete one of the biggest mistakes is   _  .", "options": ["forgetting his goals when competing", "worrying about his not winning", "carrying his goals into the competition", "paying too much attention to the result"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1037, "question": "There are 132 rooms, 32 bathrooms, and 6 floors to accommodate all the people who live in, work in, and visit the White House. There are also 412 doors, 147 windows, 28 fireplaces, 7 staircases, and 3 lifts. At various times in history, the White House has been known as the \"President's Palace\", the \"President's House\", and the \"Executive Mansion\". President Theodore Roosevelt officially gave the White House its current name in 1901. The White House receives approximately 6,000 visitors a day. With five full-time chefs, the White House kitchen is able to serve as many as 140 guests and hors d'oeuvres to more than 1,000 people. The White House requires 570 gallons of paint to cover its outside surface. For recreation, the White House has a variety of facilities available to people who live ...\n\nQ: Which President was in office when the decoration of the White House was completed?", "options": ["John Adams.", "John Tyler.", "Thomas Jefferson.", "Theodore Roosevelt."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 305, "question": "Israel has passed a law banning the use of underweight models in advertising. Known as the \"Photoshop Law\", it also requires that agencies tell their audience if they've digitally changed pictures to make models look thinner. The new law forbids the use of models with a body mass index of 18.5 or less, a standard based on internationally accepted measures. The figure matches the set of fixed limits by the U. S. Department of Health. The law doesn't set a money amount that can be gained in court from such a _ . Lawmakers realize that it may be a long and difficult process to prove in court that a company broke the new law, but they feel that simply having the law in place will accomplish what they want; stopping advertising companies from continuing to influence Israelis with images of unhe...\n\nQ: What is \"Photoshop Law\" about?", "options": ["Banning the use of underweight models.", "Banning underweight models in advertising.", "Banning changing pictures digitally.", "Banning models in advertising."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 114, "question": "Any high school students lucky enough to be accepted to Harvard University can easily count themselves among the country's best and brightest. The story of David Boone's journey from sleeping on a park bench to one of Harvard's dorm rooms, certainly stands out from the crowd of his peers. David, a 17-year-old senior at a MC2 Stem, a high school in Cleveland, Ohio that focuses largely on engineering and science classes with the help of a grant from the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation, was offered a full-ride scholarship to Harvard in the fall. His family life has been complicated for the past few years after gangs and economic hardships resulted in him being separated from his family and forced to look after himself on the streets and park benches in Cleveland. Because both his grandmothe...\n\nQ: Jeff McClellan was impressed by David's   _  .", "options": ["honesty and sincerity", "positive attitude towards life", "courage when facing difficulties", "great academic achievement"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 19, "question": "My legs don't do much because I have a serious disease. _ just sit there and look pretty. When people look at me, they only see the chair -- my wheelchair. I've been in one since I was 3 years old. And it doesn't matter if I graduate at the top of my class and go to law school. To some, I'll always be the girl in the chair. But I don't think of myself as the kid who can't walk. Most of my friends don't even notice the chair anymore. I'm just the girl they've been friends with. My friends are good at lifting me in and out of my small car when we go to the movies. We even took the car to the dance. One of the boys helped me out of the car and all the girls helped me to fix my dress. Even in the crowded school elevator, there's always someone around to carry me. There are a lot of things I ca...\n\nQ: Kennedy's story mainly tells us that we should  _  .", "options": ["work hard", "smile at life", "have dreams", "thank our parents"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2241, "question": "Supermarket Morrisons today announced to launch an online shopping operation within two years in a move to catch up with its web-savvy rivals. The UK's fourth biggest supermarket said Morrisons.com would offer grocery and non-food products but would take time to build from zero. As part of its online development, Morrisons - the only one of the \"Big Four\" grocers to have a significant internet business - revealed it had invested PS32 million in a 10% stake of a New York-based online grocer. The announcement came as Morrisons posted a 13% increase in underlying pre-tax profits of PS869 million in the year to January 30. Morrisons is implementing a growth strategy which is focused on expanding its e-commerce business and moving into the convenience store market. It has earmarked PS3 billion ...\n\nQ: Which would help Morrisons launch its own wesbsite in the future?", "options": ["Taking measures to beat its rivals as quickly as it could", "Offering enough grocery and non-food products from zero", "Building more convenience stores and market in the United States", "Launching an online operation with the acquisition of interest retailer"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1979, "question": "UNICEF reports that 40 million children below the age of 15 suffer from abuse and neglect. The USA National Committee to Prevent Child Abuse finds 3 million new reports of child abuse or neglect every year. According to such information on human rights abuses of children, the United Nations declared 2010 as the International Year of Youth. In answer to the common human rights abuses of young people, Dr. Mary Shuttleworth of Youth for Human Rights International(YHRI) recently completed her seventh annual World Tour to five continents in eighty days. The purpose of the tour is to promote the to tens of thousands of children and officials. According to UNICEF, 1.2 million children are illegally traded all over the world every year. Sold as goods, these children are forced into inhuman labor, ...\n\nQ: 2010 was declared as the International Year of Youth because    _   .", "options": ["3 million children reported their information to the UN", "many children are suffering from ill-treatment and neglect", "children are illegally traded throughout the whole world", "human rights abuses of young people have been avoided"], "answer": 1}]